<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="addon">
  <id>org.kde.dolphin_plugins</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <extends>org.kde.dolphin.desktop</extends>
  <name>Dolphin Plugins</name>
  <name xml:lang="az">Dolphin əlavələri</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Connectors del Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Connectors del Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Moduly pro Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Dolphin-plugins</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Dolphin-Module</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Dolphin Plugins</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Complementos de Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Dolphini pluginad</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Dolphin pluginak</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Dolphin-liitännäiset</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Modules externes de Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Complementos de Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Plugins de Dophin</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Plugin Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Estensioni per Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Dolphin 플러그인</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Plug-ins van Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Dolphin-tillegg</name>
  <name xml:lang="pa">ਡਾਲਫਿਨ ਪਲੱਗਇਨ</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Wtyczki Dolphina</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">'Plugins' do Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Plugins do Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="ro">Extensii pentru Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Модули Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Pluginy Dolphinu</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Dolphinovi vtičniki</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Dolphin insticksprogram</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Dolphin Eklentileri</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Додатки до Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="vi">Phần cài cắm cho Dolphin</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxDolphin Pluginsxx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Dolphin 插件</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-TW">Dolphin 外掛程式</name>
  <summary>Dolphin integration for revision control systems, Dropbox, and disk images.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="az">Versiyaya nəzarət sistemi və həmçinin Dropbox və disk rəqəmsal təsvirləri üçün Dolphin inteqrasiyası.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Integració al Dolphin per a sistemes de control de revisions, Dropbox i imatges de disc.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Integració al Dolphin per a sistemes de control de revisions, Dropbox i imatges de disc.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Integrace Dolphinu se systémy pro správu verzí, Dropboxem a obrazy disky.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="da">Dolphin-integration af revisionsstyringssystemer, Dropbox, og disk-imagefiler.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Integration von Versionsverwaltungssystemen, Dropbox und Datenträgerabbildern in Dolphin.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Dolphin integration for revision control systems, Dropbox, and disk images.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Integración en Dolphin de sistemas de control de versiones, Dropbox e imágenes de disco.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Dolphini lõimimine versioonihaldussüsteemide, Dropboxi ja kettatõmmistega.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Dolphin-en bateratzea berrikuspen kontrol sistemekin, Dropbox-ekin, eta diskoetako irudiekin.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Dolphin-integrointi versionhallintajärjestelmille, Dropboxille ja levykuvatiedostoille.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Intégration de Dolphin avec les systèmes de gestion de versions, Dropbox et les images de disques.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Integration de Dolphin per systemas de controlo de revision, Dropbox e images de disc.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Integrasi Dolphin untuk sistem kendali revisi, Dropbox, dan citra disk.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Integrazione con Dolphin per i sistemi di controllo di revisione, per Dropbox e per le immagini disco.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">Dolphin용 버전 관리 시스템, Dropbox, 디스크 이미지 통합</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Integratie van Dolphin voor revisie besturingssystemen, Dropbox en images van schijven.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Dolphin-integrering med versjonskontrollsystem, Dropbox og diskbilete.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pa">ਰੀਵਿਜ਼ਨ ਕੰਟਰੋਲ ਸਿਸਟਮ, ਡਰੌਪਬਾਕਸ ਅਤੇ ਡਿਸਕ ਈਮੇਜ਼ ਲਈ ਡਾਲਫਿਨ ਜੋੜ ਹੈ।</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Integracja Dolphina z systemami do zarządzania wersjami, Dropboksem oraz obrazami dysków</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Integração do Dolphin com sistemas de controlo de versões, o Dropbox e imagens de discos.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Integração do Dolphin para sistemas de controle de versão, Dropbox e imagens de disco.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ro">Integrează Dolphin cu sisteme de control al versiunilor, Dropbox și imagini de disc.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ru">Поддержка работы с системами управления версиями, а также с Dropbox и образами дисков.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Dolphinova integracija za nadzorne sisteme verzij izvornih programov, Dropbox in slike diskov.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Integrering av versionshanteringssystemen, Dropbox och diskavbilder i Dolphin</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Sürüm kontrol sistemleri, Dropbox ve disk görüntüleri için Dolphin bütünleştirmesi.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Інтеграція Dolphin з системами керування версіями, Dropbox та образами дисків.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="vi">Phần tích hợp vào Dolphin cho các hệ thống quản lí phiên bản, Dropbox, và ảnh đĩa.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxDolphin integration for revision control systems, Dropbox, and disk images.xx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">Dolphin 的文件版本控制系统、Dropbox 和磁盘镜像集成。</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-TW">Dolphin 的版本控制系統、Dropbox 與磁碟映像檔整合。</summary>
  <description>
    <p>These plugins integrate Dolphin with the revision control systems Bazaar, Mercurial and Git.  A Dropbox plugin gives action items to keep your files synced to the Dropbox service. A disk image integration plugin adds a mount or unmount action.</p>
    <p xml:lang="az">Bu əlavələr Bazaar, Git və Mercutial kimi versiyaya nəzarət sistemlərinin Dolphin ilə inteqrasiyasını təmin edir. Dropbox əlavəsi Faylları Dropbox xidməti ilə sinxronizasiya etməyə imkan verir. İSO inteqrasiyası əlavəsi disk rəqəmsal surətlərini qoşmaq və onları ayırmaq əməlini əlavə edir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquests connectors integren el Dolphin amb els sistemes de control de revisions Bazaar, Mercurial i Git. I un connector de Dropbox proporciona elements d'acció per a mantenir els vostres fitxers sincronitzats amb el servei de Dropbox. Un connector d'integració d'imatge de disc afegeix una acció de muntar o desmuntar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Aquests connectors integren el Dolphin amb els sistemes de control de revisions Bazaar, Mercurial i Git. I un connector de Dropbox proporciona elements d'acció per a mantindre els vostres fitxers sincronitzats amb el servei de Dropbox. Un connector d'integració d'imatge de disc afig una acció de muntar o desmuntar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Tyto moduly integrují Dolphin se systémy pro správu verzí Bazaar, Mercurial a Git. Modul pro Dropbox nabízí volby pro udržování souborů synchronizovaných se službou Dropbox. Modul pro integraci obrazů disku přidává možnost připojit nebo odpojit disk.</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Disse plugins integrerer Dolphin med revisionsstyringssystemerne Bazaar, Mercurial og Git. Et Dropbox-plugin giver handlingselementer til at holde dine filer synkroniserede med Dropbox-tjenesten. Et plugin til disk-imagefil-integration giver en montér- eller afmontér-handling.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Diese Module integrieren die Versionsverwaltungssysteme Bazaar, Mercurial und Git. Ein Dropbox-Modul stellt Aktionen zum Abgleichen von Dateien mit dem Dropbox-Dienst bereit. Datenträgerabbilder können ein- und ausgehängt werden.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">These plugins integrate Dolphin with the revision control systems Bazaar, Mercurial and Git. A Dropbox plugin gives action items to keep your files synced to the Dropbox service. A disk image integration plugin adds a mount or unmount action.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Este complemento proporciona a Dolphin los sistemas de control de versiones Bazaar, Mercurial y Git. El complemento de Dropbox proporciona acciones para mantener archivos sincronizados mediante el servicio Dropbox. Un complemento de integración de imágenes de disco añade las acciones montar y desmontar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Need pluginad lõimivad Dolphini versioonihaldussüsteemidega Bazaar, Mercurial ja Git. Dropboxi plugin võimaldab hoida faile sünkroonis Dropboxi teenusega. Kettatõmmise plugin lisab ühendamise ja lahutamise toimingud.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Plugin hauek Dolphin Bazaar, Mercurial eta Git berrikuspen kontrol sistemekin bateratzen du. Dropbox plugin batek ekintza elementuak ematen ditu zure fitxategiak Dropbox zerbitzuarekin sinkronizatuta mantentzeko. Diskoen irudiekin bateratzeko plugin batek muntatu edo desmuntatu ekintzak gehitzen ditu.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Nämä liitännäiset integroivat Dolphinin Bazaar-, Mercurial- ja Git-versionhallintajärjestelmiin. Dropbox-liitännäinen luo toiminnot tiedostojen synkronoimiseksi Dropbox-palveluun. Levykuvatiedostointegrointi lisää liittämis- ja irrottamistoiminnot.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ces modules externes intègrent Dolphin avec les systèmes de gestion de versions Bazaar, Mercurial et Git. Un module externe pour Dropbox ajoute des éléments d'action permettant de synchroniser vos fichiers au service Dropbox. Un module externe d'intégration pour les images de disque permet les actions de montage et libération.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Iste plugins integra Dolphin con le systemsa de controlo de revision Bazaar, Mercurial e Git. Un plugin de Dropbox da elementos de action pro mantener tu file synchronisate al servicio de Dropbox. Un plugin de integration de image de disc adde un action de montar e dismontar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Plugin-plugin tersebut mengintegrasikan Dolphin dengan sistem kendali revisi Bazaar, Mercurial dan Git. Sebuah plugin Dropbox memberikan item aksi untuk tetap menjaga file-filemu tersinkron ke layanan Dropbox. Sebuah plugin integrasi citra disk menambahkan aksi kait (mount) dan lepaskan kaitan (unmount).</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Queste estensioni integrano Dolphin con i sistemi di controllo di revisione Bazaar, Mercurial e Git. Un'estensione per Dropbox fornisce le voci per le azioni che mantengono i tuoi file sincronizzati con il servizio Dropbox. Un'estensione di integrazione delle immagine disco aggiunge un'azione di montaggio o di smontaggio.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 플러그인은 Dolphin에 Bazaar, Mercurial, Git와 같은 버전 관리 시스템을 통합합니다. Dropbox 플러그인을 사용하여 내 파일을 Dropbox에 동기화할 수 있습니다. 디스크 이미지 통합 플러그인을 사용하여 이미지를 마운트 및 마운트 해제할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Deze plug-ins integreren Dolphin met het besturen van de revisiesystemen Bazaar, Mercurial en Git. Een Dropbox-plug-in geeft actie-items om uw bestanden gesynchroniseerd te houden met de Dropbox service. Een plug-in voor integratie van images van schijven voegt een functie toe voor een actie aan- en afkoppelen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nn">Desse programtillegga gjev integrasjon mellom Dolphin og versjonskontroll­system som Bazaar, Mercurial og Git. Dropbox-tillegget legg til handlingar for å halda filene synkroniserte med Dropbox-tenesta. Eit tillegg for diskbilete gjev støtte for å montera og avmontera ISO-diskbilete.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Te wtyczki integrują Dolphina z systemami do zarządzania wersjami takimi jak Bazaar, Mercurial oraz Git. Wtyczka Dropbox daje elementy działania do synchronizacji z usługą Dropbox. Wtyczka obrazów dysku dodaje działanie podpięcia i odpięcia obrazów.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Estes 'plugins' integram o Dolphin com os sistemas de controlo de versões Bazaar, Mercurial e Git. Um 'plugin' do Dropbox oferece itens de acção para manter os seus ficheiros sincronizado com o serviço do Dropbox. Um 'plugin' de integração de imagens de discos adiciona uma acção para montar/desmontar as mesmas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Estes plugins integram o Dolphin com os sistemas de controle de versão como Bazaar, Mercurial e Git. Um plugin Dropbox fornece itens de ação para manter seus arquivos sincronizados com o serviço Dropbox. Um plugin de integração de imagem de disco adiciona a ação de montar e desmontar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ro">Aceste extensii integrează Dolphin cu sistemele de control al versiunilor Bazaar, Mercurial și Git. O extensie Dropbox vă oferă elemente acționabile pentru a vă sincroniza fișierele cu serviciul Dropbox. O extensie de integrare cu imaginile adaugă acțiuni de montare și demontare.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Эти модули Dolphin обеспечивают поддержку систем управления версиями Bazaar, Mercurial и Git. Модуль поддержки Dropbox позволяет выполнять синхронизацию файлы со службой Dropbox. Модуль поддержки работы с образами ISO позволяет подключать и отключать таких образы из меню действий.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Ti vtičniki se vklapljajo v Dolphin s sistemi za nadzor verzij izvornih programov Bazaar, Mercurial in Git. Vtičnik Dropbox pa nudi ukrepe, s katerimi lahko datoteke sinhronizirate s storitvijo Dropbox. Integracija s slikami diskov dodaja še operaciji priklopa in odklopa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Insticksprogrammen integrerar Dolphin med versionshanteringssystemen Bazaar, Mercurial och Git. Ett Dropbox-insticksprogram ger åtgärdsobjekt för att hålla filer synkroniserade med Dropbox-tjänsten. Ett insticksprogram för integrering av diskavbilder lägger till en monterings- eller avmonteringsåtgärder.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Bu eklentiler Dolphin'i sürüm kontrol sistemleri Bazaar, Mercurial ve Git ile bütünleştirir. Dropbox eklentisi, dosyalarınızı Dropbox hizmetiyle senkronize tutmak için eylem öğeleri bulundurur. Bir disk görüntüsü bütünleştirme eklentisi bir bağlama veya ayırma eylemi ekler.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">За допомогою цих додатків можна інтегрувати Dolphin із системами керування версіями Bazaar, Mercurial та Git. Додаток Dropbox надасть у ваше розпорядження пункти меню дій, які допоможуть підтримувати синхронізацію ваших файлів із службою Dropbox. Додаток інтеграції з образами дисків додає дії для монтування та демонтування образів.</p>
    <p xml:lang="vi">Các phần cài cắm này tích hợp vào Dolphin các hệ thống quản lí phiên bản Bazaar, Mercurial và Git. Một phần cài cắm Dropbox cung cấp các mục hành động để giữ các tệp của bạn được đồng bộ với dịch vụ Dropbox. Một phần cài cắm tích hợp ảnh đĩa cung cấp hành động gắn kết hoặc bỏ gắn kết.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThese plugins integrate Dolphin with the revision control systems Bazaar, Mercurial and Git. A Dropbox plugin gives action items to keep your files synced to the Dropbox service. A disk image integration plugin adds a mount or unmount action.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">这些插件使 Dolphin 整合版本控制系统(Bazaar、Mercurial、Git) 。Dropbox 插件提供菜单项以同步文件到 Dropbox 服务。磁盘镜像插件提供挂载、卸载菜单项。</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-TW">這些外掛程式將 Dolphin 與版本控制系統 Bazzar、Mercurial 與 Git 整合。Dropbox 外掛程式則提供了一些動作選項，讓您的檔案可以與 Dropbox 同步。磁碟映像檔整合外掛程式則加入了掛載與卸載的選項。</p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=dolphin</url>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image type="source">https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/dolphin-plugins/dolphin-plugins.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <categories>
    <category>System</category>
  </categories>
  <icon type="stock">system-file-manager</icon>
</component>
